Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Dockets (correspondence and other material re cases)
  - Docket #6, case #263: Christopher Boepple vs. State Board of Examiners (re state auto insurance), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 93)
  - Docket #6, case #264: Montana vs. Merlin Estep (re horse theft in Hill County), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 94)
  - Docket #6, case #269: British Oil Producing Company vs. State Board of Equalization (re royalty tax), 1936-1937 (Box-folder 100 / 95)
  - Docket #6, case #271: O.M. Corwin Company vs. State Board of Hail Insurance (re foreclosure on Sheridan County land), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 96)
  - Docket #6, case #275: Montana ex rel. School District #29 vs. Frank Cooney et al. (re Somers High School certification), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 97)
  - Docket #6, case #277: In the matter of the conflict of the boundaries between the Cherry Ridge Cooperative Grazing Association and the big flat and Woody Island Grazing Association (Blaine County), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 98)
  - Docket #6, case #279: Occidental Life Insurance Company vs. State Board of Hail Insurance (re foreclosure of mortgage on Sheridan County land), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 99)
  - Docket #6, case #280: The Brown Company vs. A.B. Wise, et al. (to quiet title on Chouteau County land), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 100)
  - Docket #6, case #281: United States vs. Thomas H. Eldridge (re condemnation of land for Fort Peck Dam), 1934-1941 (Box-folder 100 / 101)
  - Docket #6, case #282, 283: A.J. McDonald vs. Sam W. Mitchell, Secretary of State (re Initiative Measure 38 concerning state liquor control); William Matthews vs. Sam W. Mitchell (re Initiative Measure 38...), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 102)
  - Docket #6, case #293: United States vs. Sarah Appel (re condemnation of land for Fort Peck Dam), 1934-1941 (Box-folder 100 / 103)
  - Docket #6, case #295: Montana vs. Harry J. McGregor (re recovering money paid by Montana Relief Commission for medical services while he was member of Commission), 1934-1940 (Box-folder 100 / 104)
  - Docket #6, case #297: Montana vs. John W. Walker (re political libel in Miles City), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 105)
  - Docket #6, case #305: Montana vs. James Pemberton, manager of Sawyers Stores (re constitutionality of 8-hour work day law), 1936-1937 (Box-folder 100 / 106)
  - Docket #6, case #306: Montana vs. Russell M. Stevens, alias John Roberts (re attempted rape in Missoula), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 107)
  - Docket #6, case #311: Montana vs. Pedro Casaras (re murder in Sidney), 1936-1937 (Box-folder 100 / 108)
  - Docket #6, case #313: Montana vs. Lloyd Kurth (re Great Falls water department embezzlement), 1937 (Box-folder 100 / 109)
  - Docket #6, case #318, 319, 327: Highway Commission case (re removal of Rockwood Brown, H.J. McGregor, and L.J. Croonenberghs for filing false claims), 1935-1937 (Box-folder 100 / 110)
  - Docket #6, case #320: Nicholas Walters Estate, Helena, 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 1)
  - Docket #6, case #321, 322, 380: Montana vs. Harold A. Sayre; Eugene Sproul; and Leslie Gaffney (re arson in Terry), 1936-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 2)
  - Docket #6, case #335: Fidelity and Deposit Company of Maryland vs. Montana (re recovery of payment on bond), 1931-1937 (Box-folder 101 / 3)
  - Docket #6, case #338: Montana vs. Gilbert Semmens (re hunting without license in Yellowstone County), 1935 (Box-folder 101 / 4)
  - Docket #6, case #339: Montana ex rel. George Platt vs State Board of Education (re C.P.A. certificate), 1936-1937 (Box-folder 101 / 5)
  - Docket #6, case #340: Montana vs. Martin Aus (re horse theft in McCone County), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 6)
  - Docket #6, case #341, 347: Montana ex rel. Valley County Commissioners vs. Archie G. Bruce et al. (re Fort Peck taxation), 1934-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 7)
  - Docket #6, case #343: Fischer Incorporated et al. vs Shannon et al. (re music copyright law HB 396), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 8)
  - Docket #6, case #352: William Sworder Estate vs. Montana Liquor Control Board (re repairs made on Livingston liquor store), 1934-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 9)
  - Docket #6, case #356: Jacob Frank et al. vs. C.H. Barney et al. (to quiet title on Yellowstone County drainage ditch), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 10)
  - Docket #6, case #357: Montana vs. W.E. Dean and Sam I. Border (re practicing medicine without license by Bozeman osteopaths), 1936-1937 (Box-folder 101 / 11)
  - Docket #6, case #358: Montana ex rel. Harrison J. Freeman, Attorney General vs. District Court, Gallatin County (re practice of osteopathy), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 12)
  - Docket #6, case #363: Occidental Life Insurance Company vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor (re taxes paid under protest), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 101 / 13)
  - Docket #6, case #367: Montana vs. John Akers (re horse theft in Wolf Point), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 14)
  - Docket #6, case #369: Montana ex rel. Emil Jaumotte, County Treasurer vs. Roosevelt County), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 15)
  - Docket #6, case #370: Carl Christofferson vs. Chouteau County (re taxes paid under protest), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 16)
  - Docket #6, case #372: Montana ex rel. Philip O. Keeney vs. Board of Education (re dismissal from Montana State University for union activity), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 17)
  - Docket #6, case #373: Montana vs. Safeway Stores (re 8-hour day law), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 18)
  - Docket #6, case #375: Lolita Toy vs. State Board of Health (re compulsory vaccination), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 19)
  - Docket #6, case #376: John Jabs Estate vs. Cora A. Bragdon et al. (to quiet title on Flathead County land), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 20)
  - Docket #6, case #377: William Nuber vs. Montana Livestock Commission (re shipment and inspection of cattle), 1936-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 21)
  - Docket #6, case #384: Montana vs. Cleve Aldahl and E.J. Oder (re blackjack gambling game in Havre), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 22)
  - Docket #6, case #385: Montana ex rel. Northern Montana Lumber Company trustees vs. Board of Land Commissioners (re land near Cut Bank), 1937-1940 (Box-folder 101 / 23)
  - Docket #6, case #390: Melville Blackford vs. Judith Basin County (re right to repurchase land taken for taxes), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 101 / 24)
  - Docket #6, case #391: Montana ex rel. Harrison J. Freebourn, Attorney General vs. Great Western Building and Loan Association of Kalispell (re receivership), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 25)
  - Docket #6, case #392: United States vs. P.J. Wittmayer (re timber cutting permit near Fort Peck), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 26)
  - Docket #6, case #393: Montana ex rel. Valley County Commissioners vs. Archie G. Bruce et al (re Fort Peck tax case), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 27)
  - Docket #6, case #399: Montana ex rel. Fred Browning vs. State Board of Public Welfare (re Works Progress Administration (WPA)), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 28)
  - Docket #6, case #401, 403, 403, 474: Red Rock Lakes cases (re condemnation of land for Red Rock Lakes Wildlife Refuge), 1936-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 29)
  - Docket #6, case #406: Montana ex rel. Herbert A. Williams vs. Big Horn County Board of Public Welfare (re welfare rights of Indians), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 30)
  - Docket #6, case #408: Helena Automobile Dealers Association vs. Anderson Motors Company, Montana intervenor (re below-cost sale of cars to State), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 101 / 31)
  - Docket #6, case #414: New Brunswick Fire Insurance Company vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor (re employee group insurance with Prudential Insurance Company), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 32)
  - Docket #6, case #428: Montana vs. Hart Refineries (re gas taxes), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 101 / 33)
  - Docket #6, case #435: Montana ex rel. Silver Bow County vs. I.M. Brandjord (re registering of warrants by county welfare; includes survey of counties' policies), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 34)
  - Docket #6, case #436: Montana ex rel. Sportsman's Association vs. State Fish and Game Commission (re right of commission to set hunting and fishing seasons), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 35)
  - Docket #6, case #437: Springfield Fire and Marine Insurance Company vs. J.J. Holmes, State Auditor (re agents' commissions), 1937-1940 (Box-folder 101 / 36)
  - Docket #6, case #439: Montana ex rel. Broadwater County vs. Board of Public Welfare (re calling of meetings), 1937 (Box-folder 101 / 37)
  - Docket #6, case #440: Montana ex rel. Paul Casey vs. C.H. Brewer et al. (re Fireman's Relief Association), 1938 (Box-folder 101 / 38)
  - Docket #6, case #441: Montana ex rel. School district #8, Lake and Missoula counties vs. Lake County Commissioners (re creation of new Arlee District; includes school census), 1938-1939 (Box-folder 101 / 39)
  - Docket #6, case #442: W.O. Bohart vs. Montana Livestock Commission (re proceeds of sale of cattle), 1936-1939 (Box-folder 101 / 40)
  - Docket #6, case #448: Montana ex rel. John C. Dunn vs. Roy E. Ayers, Governor, et al. (re Board of Insane Commissioners), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 41)
  - Docket #6, case #449: Montana vs. Claude Robinson (re manslaughter in Glasgow; also includes material on Nashua Messenger printing case), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 42)
  - Docket #6, case #452: Montana ex rel. State Board of Equalization vs. State Board of Examiners (re court reporter fees), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 43)
  - Docket #6, case #463: Nan C. Smith vs. Lincoln County (re Pleasant Valley Forest Highway), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 44)
  - Docket #6, case #464: Montana ex rel. Nebraska Investment Company vs. Montana Liquor Control Board (re rent on building in Butte), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 45)
  - Docket #6, case #466: Montana ex rel. Mary J. Dean vs. Department of Public Welfare (re attorney fees in case), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 46)
  - Docket #6, case #468: Capitol Building refunding bonds (re legality of issuance), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 47)
  - Docket #6, case #470: Montana ex rel. T.B. Miller Jr. vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor), 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 48)
  - Docket #6, case #472: Bynum Irrigation District bankruptcy, 1939 (Box-folder 101 / 49)
  - Docket #6, case #476: Niels P. Nielsen Estate, Polson (re Danish heirs), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 101 / 50)
  - Docket #6, case #477: Montana Power Company vs. Broadwater Water Users Association (re Broadwater-Missouri Project), 1939-1941 (Box-folder 101 / 51)
  - Docket #6, case #487: Montana vs. Vaclav Raisl et al. (re taxes on Dawson County land), 1937-1940 (Box-folder 101 / 52)
  - Docket #6, case #492: Montana Dakota Utilities vs. Public Service Commission (re natural gas service), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 53)
  - Docket #6, case #501: Montana vs. Lewis A. Smith (re West Mayflower Mining Company), 1939-1940 (Box-folder 101 / 54)
  - Docket #6, case #504: National Park Bank, Livingston vs. Montana (re Columbus Irrigation District), 1940-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 55)
  - Docket #6, case #506: Tongue and Yellowstone River Irrigation District vs. Thomas B. Hyslop, Custer County Treasurer (re taxes), 1937-1939 (Box-folder 101 / 56)
  - Docket #6, case #508: Montana ex rel. Peter Ramsay vs. Board of Examiners of Photography (re licensing), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 101 / 57)
  - Docket #6, case #512: Montana ex rel. Richard A. Wilinson vs. Silver Bow County Clerk (re write-in candidates in election), 1940 (Box-folder 101 / 58)
  - Docket #6, case #518: Montana vs. James M. Simkins (re foreclosure on Liberty County land), 1940-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 59)
  - Docket #6, case #519: George F. Crosby vs. Board of Hail Insurance (re claim for crop damage), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 60)
  - Docket #6, case #525: Mary Elizabeth Newell vs. Department of Public Welfare (re recovery of old age pension), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 61)
  - Docket #6, case #532: Montana ex rel. Nellie McKnight vs. District Court, Beaverhead County (re water rights), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 62)
  - Docket #6, case #537: Montana vs. Richard C. Parmenter (re embezzlement as Hamilton city treasurer), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 63)
  - Docket #6, case #538: Montana vs. Clayton J. Jolly (re theft of compressor in Havre for use as beer pump), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 64)
  - Docket #6, case #541: Jesse R. Adams et al. vs. Ashley Irrigation District (re restoration of water to Ashley Lake, Flathead County), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 65)
  - Docket #6, case #546: Nuspred Foods Company vs. State Commission of Agriculture (re margarine), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 66)
  - Docket #6, case #552: Dept. of Public Welfare vs. Joseph Vilk (re reimbursement for welfare payments from Frederick Hitter Estate), 1940-1941 (Box-folder 101 / 67)
  - Docket #6, case #554: Edward T. Nordquiest vs. State Board of Examiners (re Warm Springs bonds), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 68)
  - Docket #6, case #555: Montana ex rel. Ray Barnhart vs. Fergus County Commissioners et al. (re tax lands), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 69)
  - Docket #6, case #566: A.L. Lendholm vs. Broadwater County Commissioners (re tax lands), 1940-1941 (Box-folder 101 / 70)
  - Docket #6, case #569: Montana ex rel. Lewis and Clark County vs. State Board of Public Welfare (re apportionment of welfare funds among counties), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 71)
  - Docket #6, case #573: David Granger vs. John McDonnell et al (re Madison County water rights), 1940-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 72)
  - Docket #6, case #574: Industrial Accident Board vs. Viking Mining Company (re delinquent premiums), 1937-1941 (Box-folder 101 / 73)
  - Docket #6, case #577: John de Kay vs. National Boston Montana Mines Corporation (re receivership), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 74)
  - Docket #6, case #580: Ted Comas vs. Dudley Jones, Prison Warden (re habeas corpus on burglary conviction), 1940 (Box-folder 101 / 75)
  - Docket #6, case #584: Ann Frischke vs. Montana (re Columbus property from Eliza Laby Norton Estate), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 76)
  - Docket #6, case #585: Northern Pacific Railway vs. Board of Railroad Commissioners (re World War II defense impact), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 77)
  - Docket #7, case #4: Montana vs. George Dunn (re burglary of Red Lodge grocery), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 78)
  - Docket #7, case #5: Montana vs. Montana Dakota Utilities (re constitutionality of natural gas distributors' tax), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 79)
  - Docket #7, case #7: Montana ex rel. John T. Bonner, Attorney General vs. William R. Taylor (re appointment as Anaconda city attorney while serving as state senator), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 80)
  - Docket #7, case #11: Aero Mayflower Transit Company vs Board of Railroad Commissioners (re constitutionality of Montana tax on interstate trucking), 1947 (Box-folder 101 / 81)
  - Docket #7, case #14: Valier-Montana Land and Water Company bankruptcy, 1942 (Box-folder 101 / 82)
  - Docket #7, case #15: Melba Clemons Boyd vs. Unemployment Compensation Commission (re reporting of wages), 1941 (Box-folder 101 / 83)
  - Docket #7, case #17: Charles E. Heisey Estate, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 84)
  - Docket #7, case #18: In the matter of shepherd Drainage District (re includsion of state land in district), 1942 (Box-folder 101 / 85)
  - Docket #7, case #22: Cahtarine Hoehn Estate executor vs. Heinrich Hoehn et al (to quiet title on Yellowstone County land), 1942 (Box-folder 101 / 86)
  - Docket #7, case #23: Joseph C. Lunsford (XL Donuts) vs. State Board of Health et al. (re packaging), 1942 (Box-folder 101 / 87)
  - Docket #7, case #31: State of Georgia vs. American Bitumulus Company et al. (re collusion in bid process for paving materials; Montana filed amicus curiae), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 101 / 88)
  - Docket #7, case #35: Montana ex rel. Paul C. Phillips vs. State Board of Education (re resignation/dismissal from Montana State University), 1937-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 89)
  - Docket #7, case #37: United States vs. Margaret Tobin et al. (re condemnation of land for Fort Harrison), 1942 (Box-folder 101 / 90)
  - Docket #7, case #49: In the matter of Miller Land and Stock Company, farm debtor (re taxes), 1942-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 91)
  - Docket #7, case #52: Montana ex rel. Helen Taylor Hautala vs. Judith Basin County Superintendent of Schools (re dismissal as Geyser teacher), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 92)
  - Docket #7, case #53: Montana ex rel. Jesse T. Grant vs. Senate of Montana et al. (re seat of Charles H. Mahoney), 1943 (Box-folder 101 / 93)
  - Docket #7, case #54: United States vs. A.E. McLeish et al. (re condemnation of land for Malmstrom Air Base), 1943 (Box-folder 101 / 94)
  - Docket #7, case #55: Montana vs. Louis Kruger Estate (re claim for reimbursement for care at Warm Springs Hospital), 1942-1949 (Box-folder 101 / 95)
  - Docket #7, case #57: United States vs. Valley County et al. (re condemnation of land for Glasgow Air Base), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 96)
  - Docket #7, case #63: Fred Giebler Estate (re German enemy alien heirs), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 101 / 97)
  - Docket #7, case #67: United States vs. Silver Bow County (re foreclosure of tax lien), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 98)
  - Docket #7, case #77: Yellowstone County vs. John Wight and Susan Wight (to quiet title), 1943 (Box-folder 101 / 99)
  - Docket #7, case #79: Montana vs. George Lively and Lulu Lively (to quiet title on Garfield County land), 1941-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 100)
  - Docket #7, case #80: Montana ex rel. Herbert Hoagland vs. Prairie County School District 13 (re nepotism), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 101)
  - Docket #7, case #82: James H.T. Ryman Estate, 1921, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 102)
  - Docket #7, case #84: Montana ex rel. Frank Johnson vs. Garfield County et al., 1943 (Box-folder 101 / 103)
  - Docket #7, case #85: Montana vs. James A. Allison (re murder in Forsyth), 1943-1948 (Box-folder 101 / 104)
  - Docket #7, case #88: Montana ex rel. Carl S. Anderson et al. vs. Thomas E. Carey, State Treasurer (re Nels Anderson Estate), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 105)
  - Docket #7, case #95: Johanna Nossen Estate (re German enemy alien property), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 106)
  - Docket #7, case #97: Montana vs. H.B. Albert, trustee John Braasch Estate (re German enemy alien property), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 108)
  - Docket #7, case #96: Walter Gatten habeas corpus (re Warm Springs Hospital commitment), 1943 (Box-folder 101 / 109)
  - Docket #7, case #100: Montana ex rel. R.V. Bottomly, Attorney General vs. Brotherhood of Taxicab Owners and Drivers (re Great Falls gambling), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 101 / 109)
  - Docket #7, case #101: Thomas E. Carey, State Treasurer vs. Liquor Control Board (re importation of liquor), 1943 (Box-folder 101 / 110)
  - Docket #7, case #107: Montana vs. L.H. Labbitt (re larceny by Hardin physician), 1944-1945 (Box-folder 101 / 111)
  - Docket #7, case #110: Montana vs. John Gussenhover (re sale of liquor to miners in Havre), 1944 (Box-folder 101 / 112)
  - Docket #7, case #128: Montana vs. Sam Mercer (re contempt), 1944 (Box-folder 101 / 113)
  - Docket #7, case #137: William Pike Estate, 1944 (Box-folder 101 / 114)
  - Docket #7, case #147: Joseph Thiebes, d/b/a Pacific Hide and Fur vs. J.S. McFarland, Montana Fish and Game Warden (re seizure of shotgun), 1945 (Box-folder 101 / 115)
  - Docket #7, case #158: Walter E. Bergman vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re mining permit on state land), 1929-1944 (Box-folder 101 / 116)
  - Docket #7, case #164: Texas Pacific Coal and Oil Company vs. Montana et al. (re production on state leases), 1945-1951 (Box-folder 101 / 117)
  - Docket #7, case #168: R.V. Bottomly, Attorney General vs. Sam C. Ford, Governor (re special election to fill James F. O'Connor's seat in Congress), 1945 (Box-folder 101 / 118)
  - Docket #7, case #171: North Butte Mining Company vs. Silver Bow County (re taxes), 1945 (Box-folder 101 / 119)
  - Docket #7, case #175: United States vs. State Highway Commission (re easements on Malmstrom Air Base), 1945 (Box-folder 101 / 120)
  - Docket #7, case #180: National Surety Company vs. Albert H. Kruse et al (re surety bond), 1946-1948 (Box-folder 101 / 121)
  - Docket #7, case #183: Daane Brothers vs. Box Elder Soil Conservation District (re contract for construction of earth dams), 1945-1946 (Box-folder 101 / 122)
  - Docket #7, case #185: Montana vs. Robert L. Knox (re livestock theft in Rosebud County), 1946-1947 (Box-folder 101 / 123)
  - Docket #7, case #188: Antonio Petrovich vs. George M. Hartsell, Deer Lodge County Sheriff (re Warm Springs Hospital), 1946 (Box-folder 101 / 124)
  - Docket #7, case #190: Montana ex rel. Handel Oil Company vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re oil and gas lease), 1943-1946 (Box-folder 101 / 125)
  - Docket #7, case #194: Duane Kirkness vs. H.C. Sailor, State Fish and Game Warden (re hunting out of season and confiscation of guns), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 101 / 126)
  - Docket #7, case #197: Henry Vinup guardianship (re commitment at Warm Springs Hospital), 1945 (Box-folder 101 / 127)
  - Docket #7, case #198: Utah Construction Company vs. State Water Conservation Board (re Broadwater-Missouri Project), 1944 (Box-folder 101 / 128)
  - Docket #7, case #201: Montana vs. Donald Donner and Clifford Parr (re kidnap and statutory rape of two girls from State Orphan's Home), 1946 (Box-folder 101 / 129)
  - Docket #7, case #202: George Williams habeas corpus, 1948 (Box-folder 101 / 130)
  - Docket #7, case #206: Montana vs. Theodore Stevens (re rape in Stanford), 1946 (Box-folder 101 / 131)
  - Docket #7, case #207: John Chovanak vs. State Board of Equalization (re gambling slot machines; includes list of all licensed slot machines), 1946 (Box-folder 101 / 132)
  - Docket #7, case #211: Montana vs. Ella E. Travis (re mortgage foreclosure in Custer County), 1946 (Box-folder 101 / 133)
  - Docket #7, case #216: Arthur Pilon et al. vs. Vivian Warren et al. (re auto tax), 1945-1947 (Box-folder 102 / 1)
  - Docket #7, case #223: Montana vs. Clifford Palen (re murder in Glendive), 1946-1947 (Box-folder 102 / 2)
  - Docket #7, case #225: Florence Clarke vs. Elizabeth Ireland, Supt. of Public Instruction (re retirement), 1945-1946 (Box-folder 102 / 3)
  - Docket #7, case #226: George Graves et al. vs. Frank Wiggin Estate et al. (to quiet title Musselshell County land, hail insurance lien), 1946 (Box-folder 102 / 4)
  - Docket #7, case #231: State Board of Equalization vs. Augusta Kohrs Estate (re inheritance tax), 1948 (Box-folder 102 / 5)
  - Docket #7, case #234: Sahoki Finley et al. vs. Robert Lambeth, Deputy State Fish and Game Warden (re tribal fishing rights on Pablo & Ninepipe Reservoir sites), 1947-1948 (Box-folder 102 / 6)
  - Docket #7, case #238: The Valier Company vs. Carey Land Act Board (re Valier irrigation project), 1948-1949 (Box-folder 102 / 7)
  - Docket #7, case #239: Montana ex rel. Lawrence E. Rich vs. Garfield County (re lessee preferential right to buy at appraised price), 1948 (Box-folder 102 / 8)
  - Docket #7, case #243: Oren McCallum vs. Elizabeth Eireland, Supt. of Public Instruction (re Charlo Heights School closure), 1947 (Box-folder 102 / 9)
  - Docket #7, case #244: H.O. Thompson et al. vs. Tobacco Root Cooperative State Grazing District (re constitutionality of grazing law), 1947-1948 (Box-folder 102 / 10)
  - Docket #7, case #247: John W. Chapman vs. State Board of Equalization (re gas tax), 1948-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 11)
  - Docket #7, case #254: Mountain States Telephone Company rate hearing, 1948 (Box-folder 102 / 12)
  - Docket #7, case #270: State Livestock Commission vs. William B. Ellis and Florence Ellis (re property settlement in divorce), 1947-1948 (Box-folder 102 / 13)
  - Docket #7, case #273: H.J. Nicol vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re cancellation of lease), 1948 (Box-folder 102 / 14)
  - Docket #7, case #274: Montana vs. Berkner McPherson (re transmission line easement across Soldiers' Home property), 1950-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 15)